[{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium leather cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium concrete cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Is the medium concrete cube lighter than the medium leather cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium leather cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium dirt cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium dirt cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium concrete cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium dirt cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium concrete cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium leather cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium leather cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium leather cube travel to quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium leather cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium leather cube collide with the medium dirt cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium concrete cube collide with the medium dirt cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the medium concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium dirt cube and the medium concrete cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium dirt cube and the medium leather cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium leather cube and the wall"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium leather cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium dirt cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium concrete cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium concrete cube and the medium leather cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium leather cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]